a1supplements.com 2017-01-31

# Privacy Statement - A1supplements

We are committed to your privacy! Because protecting the privacy of our visitors is of the utmost importance, we will never sell, transfer or otherwise give up any of your information, unless required by law. We hate unwanted junk mail or spam email just as much, if not more than you! Therefore, unlike most companies online, we will never give your personal information to other companies. You can feel safe providing information to us. Below is more information about any information we may collect: 

A1Supplements.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

We may use your current IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart.

Some A1Supplements.com pages may contain links to other sites. A1Supplements.com is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such Web sites.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and/or services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information when necessary. Contact information from the order form is used to provide receipts and to send orders to our customers. A customer's contact information is used to contact him or her when necessary. Customers may opt-out of receiving future correspondence (see the opt-out section below). Financial information that is collected is used for billing a customer for products and services he or she ordered or requested.

Sometimes, our online surveys or polls ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company or feedback. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings (see opt-out section below).

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). We use contact data from our contests to send users feedback or information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings (see opt-out section below).

**Third Party Relationships and Your Privacy**

Occasionally, we provide our postal mailing list (consisting of customer names and postal mailing addresses, but not e-mail addresses) to other companies whose products we believe may be of interest to you. In order to determine those products that we believe may be of interest to you, the information that you give us and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. If you prefer for us not to provide your name and postal mailing address to third parties, you may contact us in one of the ways provided below. 

**Public Forums**

This site maintains public chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any of your personal information.

**Security**

This site has strict security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control including 128 bit encryption SSL secure server usage when applicable.

**Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the option to opt-out of receiving any communications from us at any time. Simply contact us by sending email to unsubscribe@A1Supplements.com requesting to opt-out of future mailings and we will remove you from our contact database.
